buyhatke.com 2017-12-29

# Buyhatke | Privacy

**General**

BuyHatke is a product/service that is being given to the consumers to help them with their shopping needs. The data of the user stored in any kind would only be used for the betterment of customer experience and providing better business services at buyhatke.

You may use Buyhatke at any time without registering. When you visit our website, data is saved on our servers in an anonymous format, as is the website that you visit us from, the websites that you proceed to from our site, and your IP address. As this is being done, no personal data other than Services (Referred as per defined in Terms and Condition) which you have used.

However, we do need some personal information from you so that you can actively participate in Services. We would therefore like to request that you agree to the collection and storage of some of your data. You can revoke your consent by providing the prior notice. After 7 days, we will disable the account.

Buyhatke's Services knows that you care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This notice describes the privacy policy of Buyhatke's Services. By using Buyhatke's Services, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

Once you have registered for Services, you are asked to choose a Buyhatke user name together with a password, which then allows you to take advantage of all of the Services by overriding terms and conditions provided in that service.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Buyhatke's Services Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your utilization of Buyhatke's Services. We use the information to handle all type of activies in which Buyhatke involve which mainly includes process payments, communicate with you with any online and offline platforms about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as wish lists and customer reviews and recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve Services and platforms, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

Here are the types of information we gather.

  * **Information You Give Us :** we receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing Services for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** we receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Buyhatke's Services on other Web sites, offline and online platforms.
  * **E-mail Communications:** to help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Buyhatke's Services if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please unscribed from our mailing list through the link provided in mail.
  * **Information from Other Sources:** we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**What About Cookies?**

  1. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features offers, Recommended for You, personalized advertisements on other Web sites and affiliation.
  2. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Services essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to get offers , best deals , recommendations etc.
  3. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

**Does Buyhatke share the Information it receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. Buyhatke's Services shares customer information only as described below and with partners and co-branding organisations and in other Services, controls and that are either subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.

  1. **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:** We work closely with affiliated businesses with online and offline e-commerce web-sites for some purposes of co-branded and joint offerings. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party.
  2. **Third Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include activities in Services and promotional methods They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by concerned Indian law
  3. **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Buyhatke's Services or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  4. **Protection of Buyhatke's Services and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of Buyhatke's Services, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  5. **With your consent:** other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

We will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We have kept all the personal information private as in server, we will access this information as per detailed in this privacy policy for the only purpose to give improved services.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer. Buyhatke will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Buyhatke site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse happened due to these kind of issues.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites?**

Our site may include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags) and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

Buyhatke also displays personalized third-party advertising based on personal information about customers. Although Buyhatke does not provide any personal information to advertisers, advertisers (including ad-serving companies) may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized advertisement meet the criteria used to personalize the ad (for example, users in the Kolkata who browsed for or bought classical music). If you do not want us to use personal information that we gather to personalize the third-party advertisements we display to you, please send your name, address, email address at legal@buyhatke.com with complete concern. We will keep it for future transaction.

**What Information Can I Access?**

Services of Buyhatke gives you access to a broad range of information about your Hatke account and your interactions with Services for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. Click here to see some examples. This list will change as our website evolves.

**Examples of Information Collected**

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you search, buy, claim, post, participate in any Services or a contest or questionnaire or communicate with customer service at any Services and activities related to Buyhatke. For example, you provide information when you: search for a product; access the Services or one of our third-party sellers; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us) or your Hatke account; communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile Wish Lists or other gift registries, provide and rate reviews; and employ other personal notification services such as such as Available to Order Notifications. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as: your name; address and phone number; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been dispatched (including addresses and phone numbers); people (with addresses and phone numbers) provided in Services; content of reviews and e-mails to us; the personal description in your Hatke account; and financial information.

**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as Best Sellers; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click-stream to, through and from our website (including date and time); cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and any phone number used to call our customer service number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our website for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**Information for other sources**

Examples of information we receive from other sources which will be part of our different functions of Services:

  * Affiliate or business and co-branding activities
  * Operational activities
  * Financial services
  * Browsers and operating services
  * Web services like alexa, google analytics etc
  * Service promotional platforms like facebook, workshops etc.

All other communications are becoming the part of any activities of the Buyhatke and its Services.

**Data Protection Guidelines Changes**

We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We'll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. We'll post notice of modified additional terms in the applicable Service. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue your use of that Service.

If you have any concern about privacy at Buyhatke, please e-mail us at support@buyhatke.com a thorough description and we will try to resolve the issue for you. If you need notification for modification and changes send your name, complete address (including Pin Number) and email address at legal@buyhatke.com

**Co-Branded and Joint Offerings**

In the future we may offer joint or co-branded products and services such coupons, various products and also some offline ventures, this improvement will be done only for the benefits of shopping services. To provide the improved version, we can utilize your personal data.

**Information You Can Access**

Examples of information you can access easily at Services of Buyhatke includes

  1. Up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications and personalized advertising preferences, address book );
  2. Payment settings (including credit-card information and gift certificate, gift card and checque balances); e-mail notification settings (including Alerts, Available to Order notifications, Delivers, Recommended for You and newsletters);
  3. Recommendations (including recent product-view history, prior-order history and Favorites);
  4. Wish Lists and Your Profile (including your product Reviews, Requests and Recommendations, your guides, personal profile, people you tagged as interesting, and Friends).

**When information is accessed from mobile apps**

We include some third party SDKs which might also collect some personally identifiable information (PII) about you. This may include but not restricted to your email id, phone number, IP address, android ID, IMEI etc.

In case of the [mobile app](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.app.buyhatke) we also work with mobile network operators and OEMs in order to ensure the best experience for the users. We run giveaways where we ensure a user can avail the offer based on terms and conditions.. For that : 

  * The mobile network operator may collect and use unique identifiers in order to maintain the security of the account.
  * The mobile network operator reserves the right to disclose any information provided by with respect to unique identifiers to law enforcement authorities, government officials or other third-parties if the mobile network operator believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary or appropriate to enforce and/or verify compliance with any part of these Terms and Conditions, or for mobile network operators to comply with any legal process.
  * You agree to use the Application in compliance with these usage rules. The mobile network operator reserves the right to modify the usage rules at any time.
